Daniel Beccaria | Los Angeles, CA | 267.402.7385

beccdaniel@gmail.com | Github | Website

Profile:

I am a Javascript developer who focuses on modern front end tools such as React and Webpack. I consistently apply design systems, accessibility best practices, and serverless technology to make sure my products are fast, scalable, and can be used by anyone. I currently offer my services to non-profit projects in an effort to grow my skills and make a difference in the world at large.

Projects

10thWorldServers: A SaaS product that pulls in data using Azure Functions into a GatsbyJS front end.

<u>GSI</u>: Germ Science Investigation is a gamified learning experience built around teaching people to be safe during a pandemic.

<u>IP-Address-Tracker</u>: Making use of leaflet and a geolocation API users can use the search bar feature to reveal information about an ip address or domain name.

Previous Work Experience

LOCI May 2021 - Present

LOCI is a technology company that creates SaaS products which streamline and gamify safety training. I currently work here as a React developer on their game engine core, administrative website, and SaaS products. I work with serverless backend technologies to bring live data into feature rich front-ends.

Jensen + Partners March 2021 - April 2021

I was brought on to update/upgrade their wordpress website as an administrator and programmer and was responsible for reviewing the existing codebase along with correcting problems with the performance of their site along with improving SEO and assessing any other issues. Addressed security concerns and corrected vulnerabilities.

Mentalogue July 2020 - June 2021

Mentalogue is an organization that seeks to create greater access to mental health services in Malaysia. I'm primarily responsible for maintaining and updating their Wordpress website. I use CSS, custom templates, and create custom themes for various aspects of their website.

Education

Penn LPS Coding Bootcamp, Philadelphia — *Certificate*

June 2019 - September 2019

Rigorous training in the latest technologies used in the field such as React, NodeJS, MongoDB, and others. Collaborated with other students on projects and other assignments, gained a reputation as a valued member of the class.

Temple University, Philadelphia, PA — Sociology

August 2011 - May 2013

SKILLS

CSS

JavaScript

ReactJS

REST API's

NodeJS

Docker